CONTACT

- (+64) 022 0977 174
- github.com/vera-connell
- finn.bc@protonmail.com
- Wellington, New Zealand
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/vera -connell-5a3063283/

TECHNOLOGIES

- Node.js
- Ruby on Rails
- React
- Redux
- SCSS
- SQLIT3
- TypeScript

EDUCATION

Certificate of Applied Software Development

Dev Academy Aoteoroa March 2023 - July 2023

Bachelor of Science (To be Completed)

Victoria University of Wellington July 2018 - December 2019 Decided on a career change more suited to my passions.

INTERESTS

- · Trail Running
- Surfing
- Reading
- · Ski Touring

Vera Connell

Web Developer

PROFILE

I'm a web developer who is always excited to meet the challenges proposed by this rapidly evolving sector.

I have huge enthusiasm for picking up new technologies and using them to solve problems elegantly and innovatively, driven by a sense of fun and curiosity. I'm attracted to the development sector because of the wealth of opportunities that connect to new skills and personal growth.

I've been an instrumental part of many teams across a wide variety of organizations, and those who work with me highly regard my combination of interpersonal skills, independence and initiative. My ability to quickly upskill and begin working alongside existing teams has been greatly appreciated by my colleagues.

EXPERIENCE

Student at Dev Academy

Wellington

Mar 2023 - Jul 2023

- Quickly upskilled, becoming confident in a full Node.js stack in just 9 weeks.
- Worked in a variety of exciting and dynamic teams, effectively employing agile project management strategies in a variety of roles.
- Developed outstanding project planning and conflict resolution skills.
- Self educated on the Ruby on Rails framework, building an
 effective restful API and image hosting server in just a week
 of independent learning.

Workshop Assistant

The English Craftsman | Wellington

Apr 2022 - Mar 2023

- Worked in a variety of challenging and quickly evolving teamworking environments.
- Took on responsibilities to solve problems independently in a variety of new and difficult situations.

Barista

The Coffee Dojo | Wanaka

May 2021 - Dec 2021

- Became part of a highly engaged client community, cultivating excellent client relation skills.
- Regularly trusted with sole responsibility for business operations, including maintenance of business assets and managing cash.
- Received the opportunity to develop my skills as a barista to an extremely high level because of my passion for the craft.